popjolly.com 2012-12-14

# Privacy Policy

PopJolly is committed to protecting you and your family’s personal information. We want our services to be safe and enjoyable environments for everyone. This page answers some important questions about how we can collect, use and protect your personal details. Elsewhere on the site,

 **What information does PopJolly collect about me?**

When you interact with PopJolly we sometimes receive personal information about you.

For example, if you write to us or sign up to a newsletter, you might tell us who you are, how we can contact you and what you think of PopJolly and its services.

When you use PopJolly online services, we use cookies and collect IP addresses.

 **How do we use your information?**

 **We will use your personal information for a number of purposes including the following:**

To contact you (for example, we might call you if you text in to one of our radio programmes)
To provide you with services (eg to send you a newsletter or a news alert, if you have asked for them)
To personalise the way PopJolly content is presented to you (eg if you tell us your post code we may use this information to customise your view of PopJolly homepage so that you always see the local weather for your area.)

We will keep your information confidential and generally we will only use your information within PopJolly. However, we sometimes use third parties to provide services on our behalf, for example independent producers who make programmes for us.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

 **Your data protection choices**

We won’t contact you for marketing purposes, or promote new services to you unless you specifically agree. You can opt-out of receiving direct marketing from us at any stage.

You may choose to reduce the number of cookies you receive from us.

How to reach us

If you have any questions or comments about PopJolly’s Privacy Policy please contact us via the form below.

## Contact Us

Required fields are marked *.
